[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The distribution of this substance into water is often deadly for seabirds as it destroys the structure of its feathers.  Thus cold water quickly reaches the skin and the bird often freezes to death.", "correct_answer": "Oil", "incorrect_answers": ["Carbon dioxide", "Carbon monoxide", "Pesticides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie can the following conversation be heard? \nSir Leigh Teabing: And this is from the gospel of Mary Magdalene herself. \nSophie Neveu: She wrote a gospel? \nRobert Langdon: She may have.", "correct_answer": "The Da Vinci Code", "incorrect_answers": ["The Seventh Sign", "Angels and Demons", "Passion of Christ"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following volcanoes caused the most deaths?", "correct_answer": "Mount Tambora", "incorrect_answers": ["Taal", "Mount Etna", "Mauna Loa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used in Chateaubriand?", "correct_answer": "beef", "incorrect_answers": ["lamb", "pork", "deer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who plays Dr. Norman in What Lies Beneath, is also a licensed pilot of both planes and helicopters.", "correct_answer": "Harrison Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["John Travolta", "Anthony LaPaglia", "Ralph Finnes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the term baseball diamond denote?", "correct_answer": "Baseball field", "incorrect_answers": ["An award", "A female baseball player", "A title given to the greatest baseball players"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country does the River Po rise?", "correct_answer": "Italy", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Belgium", "Switzerland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Kremlin, a historic fortified complex at the heart of Moscow, overlooks this square to the east.", "correct_answer": "Red Square", "incorrect_answers": ["Black Square", "Azadi Square", "Palace Square"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Stereopsis is a process in visual perception giving the organism a sensation of what?", "correct_answer": "Depth", "incorrect_answers": ["Color", "Width", "Movement"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term encephalon, defined as the brain of a vertebrate, derives from a Greek word which means what?", "correct_answer": "In the head", "incorrect_answers": ["In the mind", "Forehead", "In the backbone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the prevailing religion in Sweden?", "correct_answer": "Lutheranism", "incorrect_answers": ["Eastern Orthodoxy", "Protestantism", "Roman Catholicism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What job did movie character Joe Dirt get to earn money to hire a sketch artist?", "correct_answer": "at an oil rig", "incorrect_answers": ["in a diamond mine", "in a fast food restaurant", "at a cattle ranch"]}]